catchfree.com 2018-07-29

# Privacy Policy – Collect, Analyze and Activate on User Feedback with Qualaroo

This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected, used and disclosed by Qualaroo with respect to the access and use of our website and our services. This Privacy Policy doesn’t apply to any third-party websites, services or applications that you may access through our services.

## Information We Collect

### Non-Personally-Identifying Information

Like most website operators, Qualaroo collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Qualaroo’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Qualaroo’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Qualaroo may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website or services. Qualaroo also collects information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Qualaroo does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the circumstances described below.

### Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Qualaroo’s websites choose to interact with Qualaroo in ways that require Qualaroo to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Qualaroo gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to create surveys to provide their email address. Qualaroo collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Qualaroo. Qualaroo does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

## Information Collected for Others

Through our services our customers can collect information about how their end users use their websites, as well as how those websites are performing. Our customers determine the types of data and information that is sent to Qualaroo for collection and analysis. The collection of this data and information by our customers is subject to their own privacy policy. Because our customers have the sole discretion to determine what data and information is collected about or from its users, our Privacy Policy does not apply to any end user data that we may collect, obtain, or access in connection with operating our service on behalf of our customers. We ask that our customers abide by all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including laws relating to privacy and data collection and post an online privacy policy that provides users with clear notice of its practices regarding data collection, use, and disclosure, however, we have no control over our customers’ activities or the disclosures they make in their privacy policy.

We may analyze end user data and information in the aggregate for purposes of internal research and/or to determine overall trends or metrics concerning how users are engaging with websites, and may report such general trends publicly, without disclosing any specific end user data and information.

## Cookies

Our service collects information about our customers website’s visitors using cookies. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Qualaroo also uses cookies to help Qualaroo identify and track visitors to the Qualaroo website, their usage of Qualaroo website, and their website access preferences. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies but you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

## How We Share the Information We Collect With Others

Qualaroo will not share personally-identifiable information about you to anyone, unless you instruct us to do so or if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information. If you are a registered user of the Qualaroo website and have supplied your email address, Qualaroo may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Qualaroo and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

Qualaroo may disclose non-personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Qualaroo’s behalf or to provide services available at Qualaroo’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Qualaroo’s website and services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Qualaroo discloses personally-identifying information only when (or if we believe we are) required to do so by law, or when Qualaroo believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Qualaroo, third parties or the public at large. Qualaroo may also transfer and/or provide information about you in connection with an acquisition, sale of company assets, or other situation where customer and user information would be transferred as one of Qualaroo’s business assets.

We will share the data and information we collect for our customers with that customer. We do not share any specific end user data or information with individuals or with other companies, other than with the specific customer whose website transmitted the data and information to us. We may share information about our customers and their end users in anonymous and/or aggregated form with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, research, analysis and other similar purposes.

## How to Access Your Information

If you have an account, you can access and modify the information you provided us through your account. If you would like to terminate your account, please send us a request and we will use reasonable efforts to honor your request as soon as possible. Once your account is deactivated, you will not be able to access our services or your information through your account.

## Security Measures We Take To Protect Your Information

Qualaroo employs administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, however, despite these efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. In the event that your personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify you if your personal information has been compromised, as required by applicable law.

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Policy

Qualaroo complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce (the “Privacy Shield Principles”) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States (the “EU Personal Data”). Qualaroo has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Qualaroo is subject to the investigatory and enforcement authority of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. If there is any conflict between the terms in our Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/

### Personal Data Collection and Use

This Privacy Policy describes the categories of personally-identifying information that we collect, which includes the EU Personal Data that we may receive in the U.S., as well as the purposes for which we use such EU Personal Data.

### Third-Party Agents or Service Providers

We may transfer EU Personal Data to our third-party contractors, affiliated organizations or other service providers who perform functions on our behalf as described in this Privacy Policy. Where required by the Privacy Shield Principles, we enter into written agreements with those third-party contractors, affiliated organizations and other service providers requiring them to provide the same level of protection the Privacy Shield Principles require and limiting their use of the data to the specified services provided on our behalf. We take reasonable and appropriate steps to ensure that third-party contractors, affiliated organizations and other service providers process EU Personal Data in accordance with our obligations under the Privacy Shield Principles and to stop and remediate any unauthorized processing. Under certain circumstances, we may remain liable for the acts of our third-party  
contractors, affiliated organizations or other service providers who perform services on our behalf for their handling of EU Personal Data that we transfer to them.

### Disclosures for National Security or Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, we may be required to disclose EU Personal Data in response to valid requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

### Access Rights

You may have the right to access the EU Personal Data that we hold about you and to request that we correct, amend, or delete it if it is inaccurate or processed in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles. These access rights may not apply in some cases, including where providing access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances or where it would violate the rights of someone other than the individual requesting access. If you would like to request access to, correction, amendment, or deletion of your EU Personal Data, you can submit a written request to the Qualaroo contact provided below. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity. In some circumstances we may charge a reasonable fee for access to your information.

### Questions or Complaints

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Qualaroo commits to resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Qualaroo at support@qualaroo.com. Qualaroo has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (“DPAs”) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction within 45 days after our receipt of your complaint, you may contact the EU DPAs for more information or file a complaint at https://edps.europa.eu/data-protection/our-role-supervisor/complaints/complaint-form_en. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

### Binding Arbitration

You may have the option to select binding arbitration for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances, provided you have taken the following steps: (a) raised your compliant directly with Qualaroo and provided us the opportunity to resolve the issue, (b) made use of the independent dispute resolution mechanism identified above, and (c) raised the issue through the relevant data protection authority and allowed the U.S. Department of Commerce an opportunity to resolve the complaint at no cost to you. For more information on binding arbitration, see the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield Framework: Annex I (Binding Arbitration).

## Privacy Policy Changes

Any information that is collected is subject to our Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. Qualaroo may modify and revise its Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on our website and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. Qualaroo encourages you to check back regularly for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy becomes effective will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Opt-Out of Qualaroo Tracking

## The Qualaroo team has years of collective experience in decision  
analysis and can help you design and implement questions that get the  
exact feedback you are looking for.
